# **Kevin Flynn**

Web Developer (VueJS / Django / NodeJS)

London, UK 07796977257 flynny85@gmail.com www.kubedev.co.uk www.github.com/k-flynn-webdev

#### **INTRO**

A naturally curious problem solver. 10 years of experience in the games industry animating, creating tools and improving workflow for artists and animators has given me a broad experience of day to day challenges and working in teams.

Being self driven and self taught has given me a different perspective when it comes to problem solving, which sets me apart from most other developers.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## AddIntel, UK Web Developer

Oct 2019 - Present [ Frontend Web Developer, Mailshots ]

## Self Web Developer

July 2018 - Present [ Learning full-stack development ]

# Freelance Technical Animator

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018 [ Animator, Setup, Tools ]

## 22 Cans, UK Technical Animator

July 2015 - Jan 2017 [ Animator, Setup, Tools ]

# If You Can, UK Technical Animator

May 2013 - March 2015
[ Animator, Setup, Tools ]

### Traveller's Tales, UK Technical Animator

Jun 2008 - Apr 2013 [ Animator, Tools ]

#### **AWARDS / RECOGNITION**

#### AddIntel, UK Dev of the quarter

2021 Q1 – For going above and beyond with a new role

## **PROJECTS**

## Minitask Github

A simple no-nonsense task tracker

## Daytrack Github

A day journal app to help keep track of day / weekly / monthly progress

# Pomodoro <u>Github</u>

A visually pleasing PWA timer app

#### **SKILLS**

- Design / Mockup
- Html / CSS / SCSS / SASS / Javascript
- Responsive Design
- Animation (3d)

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

- NodeJS (ExpressJS / FeathersJs)
- Python / Django
- VueJS / VueX
- MySQL / MongoDB
- Nginx
- VPS Deploy
- TDD (Jest / Mocha / Chai)
- Unity3D
- C# (Unity3D)

## **EDUCATION**

## The University of Bolton

2002 - 2006 BA Graphic Design & Illustration

#### **DAY TO DAY - DETAILS**

# AddressIntelligence, UK Web Developer

# Oct 2019 - Present

Since joining as a front-end web developer in Oct 2019 I've been helping the team move towards a new version of it's current successful live property market service. This has involved working closely with the back-end team (PHP) to ensure the (VueJS) front-end components work smoothly while still maintaining the previous functionality.

#### Duties:

- Creating components (VueJs)
  - Following a design document closely, communicating with the design department regarding possible UX issues and the API team to try to reduce unnecessary API calls.
- Creating components (VueJs Custom UI Kit)
  - I've also been helping to maintain a custom UI kit with the intention to be used across multiple projects. All items need to be fully tested and fully documented with examples and JSDocs.
- Testing latest changes thoroughly both for UI and UX issues.

# Sep 2020 - Present

I've also taken on more responsibility recently by taking over implementing designed mailshots (via: HTML/SASS/PHP) that involve a complicated process to ensure a client can mail physically or electronically a campaign anywhere in the country.

#### Duties:

- Testing latest changes thoroughly both for UI and UX issues.
- InHouse Mailshot campaigns (HTML/SASS/PHP)
  - These are almost mini websites, often done to a tight time schedule.